https://www.homeschooldiscountproducts.com/store-policy/

Reading Comprehension
Story of the U.S.A.
Change Currency
Loading... Please wait...
Reading Comprehension
Story of the U.S.A.
Store Policy
LIFELONG LEARNING RESOURCES offers the following Privacy Policy:At Lifelong Learning Resources, we understand that your relationship with us is a private matter. We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it. When you visit our website, any personal identity information that we need to fill your order - such as your name, address, phone, and especially credit card information - will be carefully guarded. We do not retain credit card numbers in a database available to others. This applies to IP address and cookies, which we automatically receive as well. Under no circumstances will we ever sell or give your personally identifiable information to anyone. We know that you care how your information is used, and we appreciate your trust that we will use it carefully and sensibly.LIFELONG LEARNING RESOURCES offers the following Security Policy:Your payment and personal information is always safe. Our Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software is the industry standard and among the best software available today for secure commerce transactions. It encrypts all of your personal information, including credit card number, name, and address, so that it cannot be read over the internet.LIFELONG LEARNING RESOURCES offers the following Refund Policy:    We offer a full refund on all books, in new condition, returned within 30 days of purchase.  Books returned from 30-90 days will receive a 20% restocking fee.  No returns after 90 days.  No returns on clearance items.  Opened software and audio CDs are not returnable for a refund.  Defective CDs may be returned for a replacement.  Please call 864-968-0391 for authorization to make a return.  Be sure to package the returned items carefully (plastic wrap is great).  If items are returned looking used or damaged, it reduces the amount of your refund to a "slightly damaged or used" item, often by as much as 50%.  Shipping costs are not refundable, either to you or from you back to us.  Refunds will be applied to the credit card you used at the time of purchase.
*Please note returns on "free shipping" orders (over $50) that reduce the order to less that $50 will be charged $4.00 for shipping out of the refund issued for the returned materials.  Also, if "Free with $50 purchase" books are ordered and not returned, there will be a charge of 50% of the retail price also taken out of the refund.LIFELONG LEARNING RESOURCES offers the following Shipping Policy:    Please be assured that your items will ship out as soon as possible, usually within 2 business days.  We determine the most efficient shipping carrier for your order.  We ship small orders via the U.S. Postal Service (USPS) and larger orders via United Parcel Service (UPS).
Newsletter signup
Name
Email
Further info
About Us
Contact Us
FAQS
Privacy Statement
Story of the U.S.A.
All prices are in USD. © 2020 Lifelong Learning Resources and Childrens Books | Sitemap
|
Powered by BigCommerce
